Go off!
Block it!
Dodge!
Dodge! Move!
One, two...
One, two, three...
Go on!
Sequence, go!
Again!
Elbow.
Higher.
Higher. Elbow.
Move, you've been on it for an hour!
- You talking to me, motherfucker?
- Fuck off!
Son of a bitch!
You did well staying out of it earlier.
I tried to escape once.
I got another 45 days.
I ended up in Cell 7,
up in Fresnes' fourth section.
I was pacing around my cell.
I'd been in the hole 3 or 4 days.
Suddenly, I saw bubbles in the john.
I walked over
and saw the snout of a rat,
crawling out.
I fed it. And I tamed it.
I had conversations with a rat.
A rat!
That's solitude and emptiness.
There's nothing, no more humanity.
Nothing but oblivion.
The void.
There's no more love.
There's nothing.
You don't belong anywhere.
You're not wanted.
Being forgotten is the worst part.
We're the forgotten.
You're alone with the wall people.
They're there, watching you.
They're all dead.
You have to resist.
It's not too late for you.
Mr. Darba,
you've been granted day parole.
You'll have certain obligations.
You must respect them.
It's important for next steps.
Good, thank you.
Hold onto this document.
It proves
you left the facility legally.
Your attendance certificate
lists your periods of incarceration.
Any questions?
Great. You may go.
Good luck for the future.
Samir Darba!
Hey, Samir!
I'm talking to you.
What?
- Farhat wants you to move this.
- I don't work for him.
Says who? Where are you going?
You don't get it.
No, you don't get it.
Tell Farhat to go fuck himself.
Farhat's gonna fuck you, bitch!
The sentencing judge doesn't like you.
He's pretty intolerant
when it comes to drugs.
I know your file well,
and I know what you've been through.
You can show the judge he's wrong.
Okay?
To do that,
make sure tomorrow goes very well.
You understand why?
Yes?
I spoke to Mr. Vasseur.
He's very clear.
If your trial day goes well,
he'll offer you the job.
This is the construction site.
This is where you're sleeping tonight.
It's a new one.
A bit further away.
These are the papers they'll ask for.
One, two… Three!
That's what your mother said?
- Why?
- She has no money.
What else could she say?
What did you do?
- Your leg's better.
- What?
Your leg seems better.
The doctor said it's not broken.
Thanks for your help back there.
- Where are you from?
- Senegal.
- Senegal?
- Yeah.
You seem okay here.
Praise be to God, I can't complain.
I came here because it was even worse
in my country.
God gave me a second chance.
Every day, I praise God.
Have a good evening, guys.
So?
The day wasn't too tough on you?
You did good work.
Would you like to join the team?
I can offer you a full-time contract.
I'll call your advisor
and sort the paperwork.
Come find me when you're released.
Thank you.
Samir!
You little bitch!
You got fucked so much in jail
that you've gone deaf!
Stop ignoring me, bitch!
I'm talking to you.
Come here!
Go around the block!
Go! Go!
Move!
Let me off!
- That was good.
- Lots of fish.
Sam! Hi, Sam!
How's my girl?
Hurry up, I'm starving!
Who do you think this is for?
Will you take me to school
this morning?
Only if you give me a kiss.
Let's take a ride on the motorbike.
Yeah! Motorbike!
You okay?
Slept well?
Not really.
And the baby?
He's been moving all night long.
What are you doing?
There are people
in Mommy’s restaurant.
Sam, Mia, Dara and the baby.
Put them in the restaurant.
Let's eat in the kitchen.
Here, honey.
Repeat.
Enjoy your meal.
Here.
Give Mommy a kiss!
Work hard today.
Love you, Mommy!
Bye, Sam!
Off you go!
See you tonight.
Your badge, please.
You can go.
Dusit Hotel?
You're French?
Wait over here.
Sombat!
My head hurts.
Got any aspirin?
Thanks.
Did you play again last night?
I'll get it back tonight.
Don't worry.
I'll help you a little
if I win too much.
Are you going to watch Sam's fight?
No. I don't want to see.
And I have to pick up Dara.
Sam, you're late. Hurry up!
Okay, put your hands together.
Let's pray.
Stay away.
I'm changing my bet.
50,000 on Sathian.
For the next three matches.
If you want more,
my door is open.
You know I need the money.
Look at his face.
Your guy is on something.
It's normal around here.
You know that.
We agreed.
Stay away from Sam's face.
Why is your guy doped?
- You used to be.
- That was before.
- Before you killed someone?
- Asshole.
Hansa!
Enough.
Let's grab a beer at Paradise.
LAND FOR SALE
Dara!
See that bar?
We'll keep it.
But I have an even more amazing idea.
A gigantic stage.
Look!
It would go from here...
all the way...
to here!
We'll put out cushions,
and do karaoke on Saturdays.
And I'll host the rest of the week.
First, our appointment.
Then, we'll work on your theme parties.
Okay?
Next, please.
- First and last name.
- Mia Tanhtham.
Are you really Thai?
Yes, my father is Thai.
My mother is French.
We're here for the property transfer.
We can pay the remaining part in cash.
When did you return to Thailand?
7 years ago, when my daughter was born.
Is he the father?
The father stayed in France.
We met here.
Look at this farang, without papers!
How do we know who he is?
- Sorry, we're here for the property.
- I still have to check your papers.
There's a problem.
The owner isn't selling to you anymore.
- What?
- I'm sorry.
Someone made him a better offer.
Next, please!
- Shit! All they want is money!
- Mia, I don't understand.
What did he say?
That we lost it?
- Someone made a better offer.
- Don't worry.
We'll just pay a little more.
We've nothing left...
Mia, it's no big deal.
Be right with you.
You okay?
Yeah.
Where is Sombat?
Out on the terrace.
You know him?
Narong?
See you there.
How are you?
Please, sit down!
Sam, is that right?
- You're French?
- I am.
Nobody's perfect.
Sombat tells me
you need a helping hand.
We're trying to buy Noï's land
on the beach.
I know it. Nice spot.
Apparently, you outbid us.
But...
you want to buy the land...
Do you have Thai citizenship?
No.
It'll be in my wife's name.
Don't worry.
You're not the first farang
to get fleeced by a pretty Thai girl.
Hey, relax. We're just kidding.
I'm sure your wife's not like that.
Hey, I'm kidding.
Can't you take a joke?
- Two noodle soups!
- What?
- More food?
- You heard us, old lady.
Two soups and that's it!
It's not like you're eating for free!
Hurry! We're waiting!
So...
Listen,
- We aren't rich but...
- Money, always money!
Why do people always talk about money?
Listen...
You really want that land?
I get it. I know what that's like.
When I first got here,
someone gave me a chance.
I met a person who believed in me.
I did a few favors,
and look at me today.
I always knew that someday,
it would be my turn
to give someone a chance.
Sam, I want that person to be you.
So, my question is...
what can you do for me?
You work at the airport, right?
You have clearance and a pass.
Move something for me,
and the land is yours.
That's impossible.
It's way too risky.
I understand.
Then, it'll cost you 30,000 instead.
How much?
30,000 or no restaurant.
What can I say?
Think it over.
I'm not asking for much.
Do it just once,
and that nice spot is yours.
Sam,
you and I are the same.
We both deserve a second chance,
don't we?
We didn't leave France for nothing,
Samir Darba?
Eat, it'll be cold.
You okay?
Damn, this is the middle of nowhere!
I'm glad you came around.
Kasem?
Do what you always do.
Don't change anything.
Follow Kim and leave the suitcase
where he tells you.
I trust you, Sam.
Okay, let's go.
Hello.
Your badge, please.
Go ahead.
Stop. Badge, please.
Stop !
Dara, wake up.
Mia!
- We're leaving.
- What's going on?
I can't explain now!
Come, honey.
Sam, explain to me!
We have to go!
- Explain!
- I will!
Take Dara into the room.
Now!
Run!
Come here!
Let her go!
Shut her up!
Kasem, let's go!
Time to go.
Goodbye, Samir Darba.
Did you eat?
- I don't know.
- Narong.
- I don't know him. Noï!
- Yes, mum?
- Hey, come on and eat some noodles!
- I don't know him.
That bastard Kasem.
Search in town.
Do you know Kasem?
Where are the Lady Boys bars?
- Do you know Kasem?
- No.
Do you know Kasem?
Where can he find him?
He loves playing the lord...
You can do anything you want
with her.
- What about these four?
- Later...
What's wrong with you?
Wait!
Your daughter is alive!
I'm a guest!
We often see little girls,
but they're not here.
They're sent to Bangkok to work.
They vanish!
Dara is not dead!
Mother?
Get back to work.
Where is he?
Have you seen her?
Please, no!
Don't be scared.
Some children arrived two weeks ago.
But they were taken away yesterday.
Out! Hurry!
Look at the state you're in.
Proud of yourself?
My daughter...
Your daughter...
You're a pain in my ass.
Look at the mess you've made.
Everything was so easy though.
We were after you.
Yes, Samir.
Small world.
Farhat never got over
his brother's death.
Remember that?
For five years,
Farhat had Kasem hunt you down.
It was pretty easy
to get Sombat to give you up.
He's a real piece of shit.
My daughter!
Your daughter?
The kid never left Bang Chan.
What a shame.
Look what you're making me do.
Hurry, children. Faster.
Daddy!
Where were you, Daddy?
I missed you, Daddy!
I thought you were dead!